Benjamin Thomas

Javascript Developer

Contact

Benjamingathomas@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/benjamingathomas/ https://github.com/BenGAThomas 334-207-6581 Marietta, GA 30066

Professional Summary

I am a junior web developer located in the Atlanta area.

I have experience in working with JavaScript, React, Next.JS, AngularJS, TypeScript and MySQL. I have a passion for learning new languages and growing my knowledge of web development and web design.

Professional Experience

2024-Present

Freelance Web Developer Atlanta, GA

Creating websites and projects for individuals and small businesses. Working on personal projects to learn new languages to add them to websites

· 2015-Present

Operations Manager One Touch Soccer Atlanta, GA

Managing and operating a soccer facility. Communicating with customers on renting the facility and ensuring all rentals and events run smoothly

· 2012-Present

Catering Manager Davinci's Pizza Smyrna, GA

Assisting customers in ordering food. Paying attention to details to ensure customer satisfaction. Leading and organizing orders so that they leave the store and arrive on time

Education

Feb 2023- Oct 2023

Web Development Bootcamp Digital Crafts

Projects

Iprep

Full stack meal prep website where you take a survey to order a meal kit

Character Builder

You can build your stats for a 5e D&D character

MLS API

Using api-football.com to get stats and team names for any MLS team

Skills

- ReactJS
- Javascript
- MySQL
- ViteJS
- HTML/CSS
- Communication
- Adaptability
- · Problem Solving
- Customer Service
- Critical Thinking
- Time Management
- TypeScript
- AngularJS
- Docker